<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Product xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Id>ATEC</Id>
	<Title>T900 Engine</Title>
	<Subtitle>Advanced turboshaft helicopter engine.</Subtitle>
	<Description>Honeywell and Pratt &amp; Whitney joined together to develop a dual&#x2011;spool engine, which uses computers to distribute load between the two compressors, and con¬stantly adjusts the load borne by each to optimize performance. This allows the engine to run cooler, reducing wear and tear. In sandy conditions, for example, the rear compressor can turn faster allowing the front compressor to turn more slowly, improving performance and allowing the front compressor to take less of a beating from sand ingestion.</Description>
	<Content>
		<Content>
			<Title>Efficiency</Title>
			<Body>Because it can run its two compressors at different speeds – optimizing engine operation – a dual&#x2011;spool engine achieves greater fuel efficiency than a single&#x2011;spool design. The T900 not only will meet the Army’s requirement for greater fuel efficiency over the current engine, it will provide a 3&#x2011;4 percent specific fuel consumption advantage over comparable single&#x2011;spool offerings.</Body>
		</Content>
		<Content>
			<Title>Power</Title>
			<Body>The T900 dual&#x2011;spool engine has 10 percent more power growth capability than comparable single&#x2011;spool offerings, giving the Army more flexibility as mission requirements evolve and change.</Body>
		</Content>
		<Content>
			<Title>Low Cost</Title>
			<Body>Dual&#x2011;spool engine architecture allows the T900 to run cooler and more efficiently. This reduces wear&#x2011;and&#x2011;tear, decreases associated mainte¬nance costs and extends engine life. The T900 offers the Army lower total cost over the life of the engine. Compared to the current single&#x2011;spool en¬gine, the T900 will save the Army a billion dollars a year after being fielded.</Body>
		</Content>
		<Content>
			<Title>Key Features</Title>
			<Body>60% more shaft horsepower
				50% more powerful
				30% fewer mission aborts
				25% more fuel efficient
				25% more growth capabilities
				20% increase in engine life
				20% less operation and support costs
				While also meeting stringent performance goals in high and hot conditions at 6,000 feet and 95 degrees</Body>
		</Content>
	</Content>
	<Video>
		<Title>Launch video</Title>
		<ThumbnailPath>Common/COM_IMG_LANC_VID.jpg</ThumbnailPath>
		<VideoPath>VideoAssets/COMMON_VID_PTP_001.mp4</VideoPath>
	</Video>
	<Actions>
		<Action xsi:type="GalleryAction">
			<Caption>Image Gallery</Caption>
			<ImagePaths>
				<string>ATEC/BlackHawk_0003.png</string>
				<string>ATEC/CA_5883_Hon_RIAT_CA3_1509.png</string>
			</ImagePaths>
		</Action>
		<Action xsi:type="TechSpecsAction">
			<Caption>TechSpecs Gallery</Caption>
			<ImagePaths>
				<string>ATEC/TEC_Infographic_8.5x11_r9.png</string>
			</ImagePaths>
		</Action>
	</Actions>
</Product>